https://ntn.ca/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICYPRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
This website belongs to NTN Bearing Corporation of Canada. Use of NTN's website (the "Site") does not require the submission of personal data. However, in order to take advantage of certain personalized features, you may be required to submit some information about you or your company. Please read further for details about our privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy"), what information we may collect, and how we use it. Use of this Site is also subject to NTN’s Terms and Conditions of Use.
Use of Personal Information
Certain features of the Site require you to provide personal or business information. This information will provide you access to email alerts and access to new tools we may offer in the future. The information you provide us helps us administer these features. This information can be changed by contacting the Webmaster of the Site by email.
Any information you may provide to third parties in the course of using the Site is subject to the privacy policies of those organizations.
No data you provide to NTN will be released to outside organizations, with the exception that NTN reserves the right to disclose user information when in good faith NTN has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (intentionally or unintentionally) NTN’s rights or property, other users of the Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. NTN may disclose user information when NTN believes in good faith that the law requires it.
Cookies
NTN Bearing Corporation of Canada’s domain and assorted microsites might make use of Cookie technology to provide an enhanced user experience.
Use of IP Address
An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Internet servers identify a computer by its IP address. NTN occasionally tracks IP addresses. NTN may use IP addresses to identify a user when necessary to enforce compliance with NTN’s Terms and Conditions or to protect our service, site, customers, or others.
Links to Other Sites
When you are on NTN’s Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond NTN’s control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.
NTN’s Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond NTN’s control. This Policy is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.
Security
NTN endeavors to provide secure transmission of your information from your system to our servers. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. NTN cannot guarantee the security of information you transmit to or from the Site. You do so at your own risk. While NTN strives to protect its users’ personal information and privacy, NTN cannot guarantee the security of any information disclosed online and you do so at your own risk.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this Site, you signify your assent to NTN’s Privacy Policy in relation to using NTN’s Site. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy and NTN’s Terms and Conditions of Use, you may not use NTN’s Site.
This Privacy Policy is subject to change, modification, or revocation without notice.
SIGN-UP TODAY
Please submit your information and preferred class dates, and we will be in touch to confirm.
Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Comments
×
SIGN-UP TODAY
Please submit your information and preferred class dates, and we will be in touch to confirm.
Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Comments
×
SIGN-UP TODAY
Please submit your information and preferred class dates, and we will be in touch to confirm.
Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Comments
×
Subscription Consent Form
First Name (required)
Last Name (required)
Email (required)
Phone Number (required)
Company Name (required)
Position Title
Address
Postal Code (required)
Country (required)
Province (required)
City (required)
Keep me informed. I would like to join the NTN Bearing Corporation mailing list.
